[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Ivy] I'm going to gain
Divine Oytengco's trust.
-[Diego] By bribing her?
-I was the one who bought that.
Ivy Aguas?
We'll work together
and we'll bring Emilia down.
We'll protect you and your kids.
Just trust me, Divine.
A CCTV camera recorded
Divine Oytengco being kidnapped.
Two men blew the tires
off the bodyguard's cars
so they couldn't follow.
[Natalie] Then force Madrigal
to work for you again.
Just kill him after the mission.
Keep an eye on Raul's group.
Find out if they're planning something.
And just like what I did to Emilia,
I will also sabotage their plans.
[Diego] Is this really Jaguar's hideout?
[Ivy] Yes, it's here.
I had them followed after
we met at the restaurant.
What did I ever do to you?
I'm your most loyal man!
[Raul] To me? Nothing.
But to my son? A lot.
Say your prayers.
Madrigal!
[Ivy] I'm just worried about Jepoy.
I hope he's all right. I hope he's alive.
-Ivy.
-Jepoy, where are you?
[Ivy] I want you to come home.
Ivy, I don't know where I am.
Surprised?
You?
[Jepoy] What do you really want?
Why did you save me from Jaguar?
I want you to work for me.
Let's take Jaguar down.
Once the case has been filed to the court,
it will then be raffled to the judge
who will handle the case.
[Georgina] Then the court shall
determine the probable cause
before they issue
an arrest warrant for Emilia.
[ominous music playing]
[door opening]
Attorney Fisher, please wait here.
Ombudsman Alfonso is on his way.
-Thank you.
We are finally here, Diego.
-Yes, Attorney.
-[door opening]
Ombudsman Alfonso.
Mr. Diego Torillo. Attorney Fisher.
Have a seat.
What can I do for you?
We are here to file a criminal case
against former governor Emilia Ardiente.
Here are some of the documents
that we found
that will serve as evidence to our case.
[pensive music playing]
[Anna] Diego is in court right now…
filing the case.
There will be bloodshed
if the Ardientes try to stop us.
Mark my words.
How are you a victim of the Ardientes too?
[raindrops pattering]
[pensive music continues]
Well, Divine…
Emilia is against
my relationship with Arnaldo.
That's it.
That's all I can say for now.
I'll help you until we win the case.
But please let me see my kids.
I want to talk to them.
[sobbing] Please.
Mrs. Emilia, Mama has been gone
for two days now.
Her closest friends are saying
she's just on a vacation
but, Auntie, look what I found.
[tense music playing]
She's not even picking up her phone.
Yeah.
I saw the CCTV footage.
Two men abducted your mom.
Mrs. Emilia, no one's
even contacting us for ransom.
What's wrong with Mommy?
Is she involved in something bad?
Please, Mrs. Emilia.
What's happening to Mommy? Why my mother?
Don't worry, okay?
But can you do me a favor?
If ever you hear anything from your mom,
can you please update me?
And if ever she calls me, I'll update you.
-Okay?
-Okay, I will.
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
[tense music continues]
[Ivy] Emergency?
What happened? Are you okay?
Somebody is snooping in my old playground.
Well, at least, you know it isn't me.
Someone is investigating
your little committee.
[Julio] They're trying to find
out how you stole funds
worth millions.
I wouldn't be surprised…
if I find out that Ms. Aguas
is behind the investigations against you!
[Emilia] Aunt Claire,
I haven't heard anything…
from Divine, and I'm getting worried.
[Emilia] Divine knows a lot
of my secrets, Aunt Claire.
And guess what?
I just saw Ivy Aguas at Divine's shop.
I have a feeling that…
someone is going to use her against me,
and that's Ivy Aguas.
[investigator] A CCTV camera recorded
Divine Oytengco being kidnapped.
[Stephanie] Mrs. Emilia,
no one's even contacting us for ransom.
[Stephanie] What's wrong with Mommy?
Is she involved in something bad?
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
Hello, Samantha?
Secure all my bank transactions
and call my former secretary
from city hall, now.
Hi, Emilia!
[tense music playing]
What are you doing here again?!
I came here to visit Arnaldo.
And, well, to check on you too.
What do you want? I have no time for this.
I have no time for you!
I have important things to do.
Hold on, Emilia. Wait.
Um, can I stay here for a while?
I want to take care of Arnaldo.
Okay, do whatever you want, Ivy!
I have no time for this!
I have important things to do!
Someone's grumpy.
Are you on your period?
Where are you going?
It's none of your business. And wait!
Just stay there.
Don't you dare move!
Don't start with me, Ivy.
[tense music playing]
Are you sure that's all of it?
Madam, these are the only files
left from when you were still mayor.
Well, keep looking! Check them one by one!
You need to check
every single one of them!
Do you understand?! Check them all!
-Emilia!
-Shred this!
Emilia, what's going on?!
I'm trying to hide any evidence
they can use against me, Aunt Claire!
Someone has been keeping an eye on me!
And who is that person?
Ivy Aguas.
[tense music playing]
[heart rate monitor beeping]
[beeping continues]
[slow tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
Hi, Arnaldo.
Do you know why I'm still here?
To keep my friends close…
and my enemies closer.
I'll be right here.
Because I want to keep an eye on you.
And to keep an eye on your mother too.
So sleep well, Arnaldo.
And don't ever wake up.
-[tense music playing]
-[beeping continues]
[tense music playing]
Ivy Aguas is back, Auntie!
She's back at the mansion!
And why would she want to be back
with all the hostility she's getting?!
Why would she want to be back, Auntie?!
Because she's keeping an eye on me!
She even went to…
-Emilia.
-…Divine's shop?
Emilia! Think straight
and go back to your senses!
Do you want to go crazy like Arnaldo?!
Keep searching! Hurry! Check them all!
Mrs. Emilia, they're gone.
Maybe Carol gave it to the woman
who came here before.
Someone came here?
Yes, but it was Carol who spoke to her.
What did she look like?
Well?!
[ominous music playing]
Oh, hi, Camia!
[tense music playing]
Emilia, what are you doing here?
I'm paying you a visit!
Is that so wrong?
No wonder I wasn't feeling well.
It's as if the devil was heading my way.
And what do you think of yourself?
You think you're a saint,
but all you are is a nosy woman.
You went through my files? Why?
To have me investigated?
Answer me!
[tense music continues]
You won't answer?
Well…
I think this will change your mind!
[suspenseful music playing]
Go ahead, Emilia! Kill me!
That wouldn't be the worst thing
your sadistic family has done to me!
You know, you are so right.
You're right.
Papa and his hitman
should have just killed you!
I don't know why you're still alive!
I won't let someone
like you put me behind bars!
Do you understand?!
Yes, but you're going to die first!
[screaming] [coughing]
[squealing]
What?!
[Loring] You bought so much.
You can't even eat half of that
-because of your diabetes.
-Kill joy! Kill joy!
Oh!
Who was that guy? He looked suspicious?
-Wait…
-Hey.
Did we leave the door open?
-Guard!
-Hurry!
Hey!
Why are you here?!
Come here!
-[clamoring]
-Wait!
You bunch of poor people!
Touching me?!
[screaming]
You!
Don't you know who I am?
I am Emilia Ardiente.
I can buy you and this hospital!
Pathetic. Oh, but wait.
Let me get my expensive bag
that you guys can't afford!
[grunts]
Don't ever come back!
She's just like her evil father!
She's Lucifer's right hand!
-Camia, how are you?
-Goodness!
I'm all right now.
[breathing heavily]
Miss Loring?
[somber music playing]
What?!
What happened to my mother?
She's fine now.
[Loring] I don't know.
If we had come in a minute late,
I don't know
what would have happened to her.
Emilia's insane.
Miss Loring, please let me
speak to my mother.
Your mom's resting now, dear.
Okay. Thank you, anyway.
All right, bye.
[somber music playing]
[sighing] Poof.
What are you still doing here?
My mission isn't finished yet.
-"Mission."
-That's why I'm still here.
Don't worry, Emilia.
I'll just finish my mission.
Okay.
You're speaking in tongues.
"Mission."
[tense music playing]
That Camia! I will kill her!
[Emilia] I will strangle her neck, Auntie!
[Claire] Calm down, Emilia.
-I can't calm down!
-[mobile phone ringing]
Hello? Yes, Attorney?
[tense music playing]
What?!
Camia Cruz didn't file
the case against me?
[Emilia] No, but you still have
to get that woman!
What?
I…
I have a case with the Ombudsman?
Who filed it if Camia Cruz didn't?
Diego?
Oh my--
[screaming]
[Emilia] That Diego, Auntie!
What am I going to do?
[tense music playing]
I need alcohol, Auntie. I need wine.
[tense music swells]
So, Ivy, I do apologize
for the late welcome.
But I appreciate the effort
that you're putting in
to take care of Arnaldo.
[Julio] How long will you be staying?
Around a week.
-One week?
-Mm-hm.
Yeah, I guess one week is enough time
to be able to iron out the kinks
in our relationships.
Right, Emilia?
Papa, having a rapport with Ivy right now
should be the least of my problems.
Just to remind you again,
Papa, I have an ongoing plunder
case filed by Diego Torillo.
And he has Divine Oytengco.
That's why they're not afraid
to file a case against me.
You know that's not news to me.
That case won't go anywhere.
Even if Judge Nazareno
is handling the case?
Our family's enemy?
Wow, Papa.
I can just imagine if this goes south.
How will this affect your candidacy?
[slow tense music playing]
Emilia.
No, thank you.
Sure?
Yes.
Thank you, my dear.
[Julio] Problems, problems…
Minor problems…
Well, I hope, Papa, it's just minor.
A minor glitch.
[tense music continues]
[car honking]
Julio Ardiente,
from the famed and fertile
lands of Poblacion Ardiente.
I heard from my fellows
that it was difficult for us
to deal with you Ardientes.
For you, there are only two things.
Money or bullet.
I see that my reputation precedes me.
But…
I'm not going to say
that isn't true, Judge.
I just have one piece of advice.
Reserve your killings for endeavors
that will advance your agenda.
Let me paint you a scenario.
Emilia will be tried
because there is strong
evidence against her.
She will be convicted…
but put in a comfortable jail.
You will lose a daughter.
But you already know
that she gives you nothing.
In essence, you lose nothing.
Why would you kill for nothing?
[tense music playing]
[Joselito] You were right.
Julio Ardiente came to me.
I told him…
the exact words you told me to say.
Thank you. Thank you, Judge Nazareno.
I regret…
not meeting you sooner.
I believe in what you're fighting for…
and your desire to expose…
…those corrupting the country.
I should be the one thanking you.
Again, thank you, Judge Nazareno.
Bye.
[suspenseful music playing]
Julio, you bastard. I knew it.
[ominous music playing]
[Joselito] Emilia will be tried
because there is strong evidence
against her.
She will be convicted.
You will lose a daughter.
But she gives you nothing.
In essence, you lose nothing.
[Joselito] Why would you kill for nothing?
Papa…
Papa, did you talk to the judge already?
Will they dismiss my case?
Am I going to jail?
[tense music playing]
[sobbing]
[dramatic piano music playing]
Mrs. Oytengco…
Diego…
I've already spoken with your children.
Huh?
You'll be reunited with them later.
Really?
Thank you so much. Thank you.
[sobbing]
[Emilia] Papa, answer me!
Sit your ass down!
And you, Ivy.
Please, join us.
What is this about, Papa?!
What are you willing to do to
make sure you don't get jailed?
Oh my, Papa!
Why are you asking these silly questions?
Not now, please!
Will you just answer
the wretched question?!
I don't know! Maybe, kill the judge?
Pay the judge? Or, kill the witnesses!
[tense music playing]
How about you, Ivy?
If you were in her shoes,
what would you do?
Get the best lawyer, Congressman.
Oh.
You, and you.
You are both very, very wrong.
[tense music playing]
Good grief, Emilia.
If it were me, I'd destroy
the person who sued you!
Goodness.
Such a simple solution.
You know, the root cause of our
problems is one and the same.
From the very start,
there's only been one thorn
on this family's side.
Diego Torillo!
[suspenseful music playing]
And I will put an end
to the life of that miserable,
wretched worm.
[mobile phone ringing]
Hello? Stephanie, yes?
What?!
Oh, really?
It's good to know you've finally
spoken with your mom.
What? Wait.
Did you just say that
she's with Diego Torillo?!
No, I'm just going to stay here. Yeah.
Good to hear from you again, sweetie.
I'm happy for you. Bye!
[slow tense music playing]
[line ringing]
Hello!
I heard Divine Oytengco
was seen with Diego Torillo.
Wait for them outside the restaurant,
then blow their car up to bits!
Make sure no one gets out alive!
Understand?!
She's high-strung.
So violent.
Excuse me, Congressman.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Ivy.
Diego.
Diego, don't go meet
Divine's children anymore.
Emilia's men are on
their way there. If we lose…
our whistle-blower,
all our plans will be for nothing.
Ivy, don't worry.
I'm with Arthur, we'll take care of it.
Diego, promise me you won't get hurt.
That none of you will get hurt.
Ivy, I'll make sure the ones
on our side stay safe.
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
What's wrong?
Emilia's men are waiting
at the restaurant.
We have to go there
and get my children out!
Who knows what Emilia will do to them?!
Don't worry. I have a plan.
Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
Are you enjoying
what you're watching right now?
You know, Papa was right.
He said, "You should
destroy your enemies."
[ominous music playing]
I should've done this a long time ago.
[tense music playing]
You must really like Diego.
Actually, you must love him
more than you love Arnaldo.
I can see it in your eyes, Ivy.
It's quite obvious.
But don't worry, it's over now.
What does it feel like to talk
when no one's listening?
Even if they kill Diego Torillo
in front of me, I wouldn't care.
I really don't.
[ominous music playing]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
Emilia's men are waiting
at the restaurant.
We have to go there
and get my children out!
Who knows what Emilia will do to them?!
Don't worry. I have a plan.
Keep eating while we're waiting for Mommy.
[mobile phone ringing]
It's Mama.
Hello, Mama?
Stephanie, you listen
to me carefully, okay?
You have to leave right now.
[Divine] Take the exit out the
back. I'll meet you there, okay?
Come on. Hurry.
Are you okay?
[tense music playing]
It's Mommy.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Divine] Let's go, let's go! Let's go!
Let's go. All set.
-Come on. Come on. Careful.
-Get inside. Hurry, get in.
Get inside. Hurry, get in. Hurry! Go!
How are you, kids?
Arthur, take care of them.
-I'll handle it.
-Be careful.
[suspenseful music playing]
[engine running]
[gunshots]
[tense music playing]
Where are they?
There's nobody there?
Oh, Emilia.
[grunts]
Papa!
Diego got away, Divine got away.
So, my case will continue?!
But you spoke to Judge Nazareno.
Right, Papa?
My case will be dismissed, right?!
[somber music playing]
Wrong.
What?
I'm not going to waste my money
or my bullets on nothing.
You've got to be kidding me, Papa, right?
You've got to be kidding me!
I'm sorry, Emilia.
I'm not kidding.
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
Emilia!
Emilia, you don't have to do this.
I need to, Auntie. I'm going to jail.
I need to leave right now.
I need to get on a plane!
And you!
Don't just stand there snickering.
I know you had something
to do with me going to jail.
Me? Me again?
Emilia, you're funny. You keep blaming me.
We were together the whole time.
How could I be involved in this?
But fine. Go. Go, Emilia. Run.
Ivy!
I have no time for this, Ivy.
Not now! Because I'm going to prison.
Papa betrayed me.
Divine and that Diego are alive!
I'm going to prison, Auntie,
that's why I have to go.
I'm leaving!
-Emilia.
-Emilia, don't worry.
If ever, I can visit you. Me and Mamita.
[screaming]
[door opening]
[tense music playing]
[door closing]
Go ahead, Emilia.
Run as far as your legs can carry you.
Emilia, please.
Please don't do this.
Emilia. Don't do this, Emilia.
Oh my goodness.
[tense music continues]
[mobile phone ringing]
Ivy?
Hello? Where are you?
We're here.
Hurry up, Emilia's escaping.
What?
[suspenseful music playing]
You won't get away, Emilia.
[Julio] Open that gate.
What do you want?
Give us Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
[scoffs]
Who gave you the right to
tell me to give you my daughter?
Where is Emilia
Ardiente-Torillo, Congressman?
She isn't here.
We have a warrant for her arrest.
I don't care about your warrant of arrest.
Julio!
-Julio, what's happening?!
-I'm sorry, Congressman.
But, we received information
that your daughter is here with you.
[tense music playing]
Come on. Let's search the place.
Didn't you hear me?!
Get out of my property!
-Julio!
-You bastards!
[Claire] Wait!
-Diego.
-Ivy.
-Emilia went that way.
-Follow me!
Good luck, Emilia.
Hello?
Stephanie?
Where are you?!
I need the ticket!
[police siren wailing]
Mrs. Emilia!
Don't try to escape! Just come with us!
[panting] No.
Come on! Hurry!
Emilia.
Give up.
[dramatic music playing]
Emilia Torillo.
You are under arrest for plunder.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you can't afford an attorney,
one will be provided by the government.
You can't do this to me!
Don't you know who I am?!
I'm Emilia Ardiente!
You cannot do this to me!
Papa!
Why are you just standing there?!
-You have to do something.
-Cuff her!
-No!
-There's nothing I can do.
No! Please! Papa! Do something!
I'm sorry, Emilia.
-[Julio] Please don't hurt her.
-Auntie!
[tense music playing]
Auntie! Papa, please!
[tense music continues]
[Ivy] You basked in your wealth.
Wealth that you used
to kill my father…
[car crashing]
…to hire someone to rape my mother…
[suppressed gunshots]
…and to intimidate others.
But you can't buy justice.
Now it's time for you to face
the consequences of your crimes.
[tense music playing]
Ma'am! Who filed the case against you?
Is there any truth to their accusations?
Ma'am, please answer the question!
-Out of the way.
-Ma'am, what did you do?
Why were you arrested?
[reporters clamoring]
Ma'am, is there any truth
to their accusations?
[reporters clamoring]
I have no intentions of going
to that dingy, stinking jail.
What?!
Earlier, you hid Emilia from the police.
Julio, your daughter needs you.
I don't have a daughter who's a criminal.
And, most importantly,
I don't have a daughter
who's dumb enough
to get caught for her crimes!
Okay, I must admit…
I tried to hide her
when I thought there was
the slimmest chance
that she might be able to escape.
But now that everybody's
feasting on her downfall,
I won't dirty my hands
with the mess she made!
Well then, whether you like it
or not, I'm going to her.
Go ahead! I'm not going to stop you!
Anyway, what else can you do?
What else can you offer her
besides your cheap sympathy?
I won't stoop to your level.
You're worse than the devil himself.
That hurts!
Well…
What a softie.
But anyway…
You know, I realized…
she's not an Ardiente.
But seriously, Congressman,
what do you plan to do with Emilia?
Emilia…
will have a staycation in jail
for as long as necessary.
Now, when I think and know
that the time is right,
I will bail her out myself.
Well…
It will all depend on how things turn out.
[chuckles]
Poor Emilia.
[somber music playing]
Emilia has been arrested!
Thank you so much, Diego!
Thanks to you and Ivy!
We should be the ones thanking you.
Thank you for the trust
you gave me and Ivy.
But it doesn't end here.
We need to put Emilia Ardiente in prison.
Attorney Fisher called too.
She'll schedule trials
as soon as possible.
Then, until the trials start,
we'll be keeping you from Emilia.
Don't worry.
We're here to protect you.
Thank you.
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ivy] As much as I'd like
to pity you, Emilia, I won't.
Because you deserve to be in prison.
And I won't even celebrate this
because seeking justice isn't a game.
It's a responsibility.
[tense music playing]
Come in, Madam.
For now, you'll be staying
in the Chief's office.
Do you know who this is?
Excuse me, Madam. Please fill this up.
You haven't even answered my question!
How rude!
I was asking if you knew who this was.
Yes. You're Mrs. Emilia,
former Mayor and Governor
of Poblacion Ardiente.
But right now,
we're just following our SOP.
And, you have to comply with them.
Excuse me.
I don't have to learn your stupid SOP
because I'm getting out of here!
I'm not staying here!
So, don't you ever teach me to
follow your stupid SOP, okay?!
Now…
If you don't treat me with respect,
I'll have to book you for a "good job".
Do you know what that means?
I can order someone to kill you
and your family!
Then, when the deed is done,
I'll say "good job".
Now, are you going to
treat me with respect,
or are you going to get the "good job"?
[slow tense music playing]
Lily…
I hope that Julio doesn't
have that daughter of his freed.
I've had it with that Emilia.
I might just give her a piece of my mind.
Mom…
You were just discharged
from the hospital.
Don't worry about it.
I assure you Julio
won't have Emilia freed.
And even if he does, I'll stop him.
I'll find a way to protect you from her.
And I will, Mom. I promise you that.
[pensive music playing]
I'm sorry, Lily.
I just can't help but worry
that she'll escape from prison.
Like, what if her men are just out there,
waiting for the right time to strike?
To hurt us?
To hurt you?
Mom…
Emilia Ardiente can't lay a hand on me.
And, definitely not you.
And, in case she does,
I'll do everything in my power
to make her own father
betray her, to make her
lose her title as an Ardiente.
There's no way Emilia can run from me now.
This is revenge for everything
she's done to our family.
I'm going to make sure
that Emilia rots behind bars,
both her body and her soul.
-Emilia…
-Auntie! Auntie!
Are you okay?
Auntie, I'm glad you came.
Where's Papa and my lawyer?
[suspenseful music playing]
Auntie, don't tell me you're not
going to bail me out of here?
So, why did you even come here?
I'm just here to comfort you.
Auntie, it's not like I'm going to die.
What I need is I want to get out of here!
I don't belong here!
Auntie…
I'm sorry.
I don't like it here!
Madam, the Chief said
he needs you to leave this room.
We'll be taking you to your cell.
-Wait, hold on.
-Let's go.
You can't lock me up!
-Sorry, Madam.
-Wait! Auntie!
Don't touch me!
-Please just cooperate.
-Emilia.
-Please come with us.
-Auntie!
-Please wait.
-Don't lock me up! You can't!
[dramatic music playing]
[somber music playing]
[screaming]
There's a cockroach!
[squealing]
Get me out of here!
I can't do this. I don't belong here!
Cockroach!
[dramatic music playing]
Why are you punishing your own daughter?
Just shut up!
You'll eventually meet your maker.
50 million pesos.
If I help you, what will I get in return?
I will become king and you will be queen.
There's something you need to know.
Who are you talking to?
Please help me.
I'll help you, but on one condition.
Turn your back on your father.
[gunshot]
-[gunshot]
-[squeals]
Dante.
Dad?
[theme music playing]